ILGWU Political/Legislative Department, Evelyn Dubrow Papers 5780/142
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
ILGWU Political/Legislative Department, Evelyn Dubrow Papers
1976-1996
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Dubrow, Evelyn
International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union
5780/142
28 cubic feet
28 linear ft.
Records (documents).
This collection contains Evelyn Dubrow's correspondence, memoranda, and reports relating to her lobbying activities in Washington, D.C. in series of legislative files and subject files.
5510296
Biographical / Historical
The International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union was once one of the largest labor unions in the United States founded in 1900 by local union delegates representing about 2,000 members in cities in the northeastern United States. It was one of the first U.S. Unions to have a membership consisting of mostly females, and it played a key role in the labor history of the 1920s and 1930s. The union is generally referred to as the "ILGWU" or the "ILG". The ILGWU grew in geographical scope, membership size, and political influence to become one of the most powerful forces in American organized labor by mid-century. Representing workers in the women's garment industry, the ILGWU worked to improve working and living conditions of its members through collective bargaining agreements, training programs, health care facilities, cooperative housing, educational opportunities, and other efforts. The ILGWU merged with the Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers Union in 1995 to form the Union of Needle trades, Industrial and Textile Employees (UNITE). UNITE merged with the Hotel Employees and Restaurant Employees Union (HERE) in 2004 to create a new union known as UNITE HERE. The two unions that formed UNITE in 1995 represented only 250,000 workers between them, down from the ILGWU's peak membership of 450,000 in 1969.
Biographical / Historical
Evelyn Dubrow was born in Passaic, New Jersey, in 1911. A graduate of New York University, Dubrow worked as a report for The Morning Call (Patterson, N.J.) and Secretary of the New Jersey organization of the American Newspaper Guild from 1943 to 1946, before becoming Educational Director for the Textile Workers Union of American in New Jersey. In 1949, she became New York state Director for Americans for Democratic Action. In 1956, she was named the ILGWU's chief lobbyist in Washington, D.C. Dubrow worked as Legislative Representative and Executive Secretary of the Political Department of the ILGWU, and continued her work after the union's merger with the Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers of America to create the Union of Needletrades, Industrial, and Textile Employees (UNITE). Dubrow died in Washington D.C., in 2006.
Biographical / Historical
The Political Department of the ILGWU was founded in 1947, under the direction of Gus Tyler. Its primary function was to engage union members and their families in political issues at the local, state, and national levels. This engagement was achieved through conferences, publications, and other communications. Educational work was a hallmark of the department, as were the department's legislative monitoring, research activities, and organizing for electoral campaigns.
David Wells joined the Political Department in 1952, eventually becoming Assistant Director. In 1956, Evelyn Dubrow was named the ILGWU's chief lobbyist in Washington, D.C., and became a well-known fixture on Capitol Hill.
Scope and Contents
The Political Department records are constituted of two accessions of Evelyn Dubrow papers and one accession of records from the department. Included are correspondence and memoranda, reports of lobbying activities, subject files on states and ILGWU affiliates, receipts for campaign contributions, ephemera from political campaigns.
These records are complemented by one accession of the Gus Tyler papers (5780/088) that includes records relating to his work as founding director of the Political Department, in addition to some of his other activities relating to the union. An oral history interview with David Wells (6036/076), in which the former Assistant Director discusses his work with the Union and in New York City, also complements the records of the Political Department.
Taken together, these materials, the Political Department records, Evelyn Dubrow papers, Gus Tyler papers, and the David Wells interview, document a considerable range of the Political Department's work from its founding in 1948 to its merger with ACTWU in 1995.
This collection contains Evelyn Dubrow's correspondence, memoranda, and reports relating to her lobbying activities in Washington, D.C. Also included in this collection are letters and receipts documenting campaign contributions, alphabetical files on states, as well as files on local unions, joint boards, and regional departments. The records of the Political Department also contain ephemeral printed material relating to political campaigns, including pamphlets, posters, and fliers.
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: 5780: ILGWU records 5780/103: ILGWU Political Department Records 5780/119: ILGWU Political Department, Evelyn Dubrow Papers 5780/088: ILGWU Gus Tyler Papers 6036/076 OH: Daniel Soyer ILGWU Heritage Project 6036/080: Evelyn Dubrow papers 6036/080 P: Evelyn Dubrow Photographs
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives 227 Ives Hall Tower Road Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183 kheelref@cornell.edu https://catherwood.library.cornell.edu/kheel/
Compiled by:
C. Berne, December 10, 2003
EAD encoding:
Kheel Staff, April 15, 2019
Women's clothing industry -- United States; Clothing industry -- Labor unions -- United States; Clothing workers -- United States; Industrial relations -- United States; Dubrow, Evelyn.
5510296
- Jay Mazur Correspondence, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Justice, 1989-1990 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Resolutions, 1988-1989 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Homework, 1987-1989 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Homework, 1988-1989 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Letters of Congratulations to Congressmen, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Evelyn Dubrow Correspondence, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Evelyn Dubrow Correspondence, 1981-1989 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Blank Receipt and Disbursement Forms (Box 1, Folder 9)
- AFL-CIO Committee on Political Education, 1988 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Democratic National Committee, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- ILGWU Finances, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 12)
- Coalition of Labor Union Women (CLUW), 1988-1990 (Box 1, Folder 13)
- Newsletters and Notices from Congressmen, 1988-1989 (Box 1, Folder 14)
- Daily Schedule, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  Scope and Contents
  February-December
- Evelyn Dubrow Correspondence, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 16)
- Statements by AFL-CIO Executive Council, 1988-1989 (Box 1, Folder 17)
- AFL-CIO News, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 18)
- AFL-CIO Legislative Alert, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 19)
- Child Labor Articles, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 20)
- Homework and Minimum Wage, 1989 (Box 2, Folder 1)
- Jay Mazur, 1989 (Box 2, Folder 2)
- Miscellaneous Committee Correspondence, 1989 (Box 2, Folder 3)
- Congressmen Jim Florio and Jim Courter, 1989 (Box 2, Folder 4)
- Labor-Industry Coalition for International Trade (LICIT), 1989 (Box 2, Folder 5)
- Voter Registration Material, 1989 (Box 2, Folder 6)
- Fundraisers and Contributions, 1988-1989 (Box 2, Folder 7)
- Miscellaneous Memorandums, 1988-1990 (Box 2, Folder 8)
- Newsletters with Dinkins Articles, 1989 (Box 2, Folder 9)
- National Abortion Rights Action League (NARAL Foundation), 1989 (Box 2, Folder 10)
- ILGWU Finance Department, 1989 (Box 2, Folder 11)
- ILGWU Finance Department, 1989 (Box 2, Folder 12)
- ILGWU Finance Department, 1989 (Box 2, Folder 13)
- ILGWU Finance Department, 1989 (Box 2, Folder 14)
- ILGWU Finance Department, 1989-1990 (Box 2, Folder 15)
- ILGWU Finance Department, 1989 (Box 2, Folder 16)
- United States Senate, 1989 (Box 2, Folder 17)
- Delivery Receipts, 1984 (Box 2, Folder 18)
- Social Services Task Force, 1988-1989 (Box 2, Folder 19)
- Civil Rights Memorial, 1987-1989 (Box 2, Folder 20)
- Child Labor and Day Care, 1988-1989 (Box 2, Folder 21)
- United States Trademark Association, 1988 (Box 2, Folder 22)
- Voters for Choice, 1989 (Box 2, Folder 23)
- Washington Social Legislation Bulletin, 1988 (Box 2, Folder 24)
- Women's and Children's Apparel Labor Management Committee, 1989 (Box 2, Folder 25)
- Women's Research and Education Institute (WREI), 1987-1989 (Box 2, Folder 26)
- Receptions for Congressmen, 1988 (Box 3, Folder 1)
- Congress - Contributions and Receptions, 1988 (Box 3, Folder 2)
- Congress - Contributions and Receptions, 1988 (Box 3, Folder 3)
- Congress - Contributions and Receptions, 1988 (Box 3, Folder 4)
- Congress - Contributions and Receptions, 1988 (Box 3, Folder 5)
- ILGWU Campaign Committee, 1988 (Box 3, Folder 6)
- ILGWU Campaign Committee, 1988 (Box 3, Folder 7)
- ILGWU Campaign Committee, 1988 (Box 3, Folder 8)
- ILGWU Campaign Committee, 1988 (Box 3, Folder 9)
- ILGWU Campaign Committee, 1988 (Box 3, Folder 10)
- ILGWU Campaign Committee, 1988 (Box 3, Folder 11)
- ILGWU State and Local Election Fund, 1988 (Box 3, Folder 12)
- Congress - Contributions and Receptions, 1987 (Box 3, Folder 13)
- Congress - Contributions and Receptions, 1987 (Box 3, Folder 14)
- Congress - Contributions and Receptions, 1987 (Box 3, Folder 15)
- Congress - Contributions and Receptions, 1987 (Box 3, Folder 16)
- Congress - Contributions and Receptions, 1987 (Box 4, Folder 1)
- ILGWU Campaign Committee, 1987 (Box 4, Folder 2)
- ILGWU Campaign Committee, 1987 (Box 4, Folder 3)
- ILGWU Campaign Committee, 1987 (Box 4, Folder 4)
- ILGWU Campaign Committee, 1987 (Box 4, Folder 5)
- ILGWU Campaign Committee Reports of Receipts and Disbursements, 1987-1988 (Box 4, Folder 6)
- Contributions to Congress, 1987-1988 (Box 4, Folder 7)
- Contributions, 1987 (Box 4, Folder 8)
- Congress - Contributions and Receptions, 1987-1989 (Box 4, Folder 9)
- Congress - Contributions and Receptions, 1988 (Box 4, Folder 10)
- Thank You Letters for Contributions, 1988 (Box 4, Folder 11)
- Thank You Letters for Contributions, 1988 (Box 4, Folder 12)
- Congress - Contributions and Receptions, 1987-1988 (Box 4, Folder 13)
- Congress - Contributions and Receptions, 1987-1988 (Box 4, Folder 14)
- Bills and Amendments, 1985 (Box 5, Folder 1)
- "C" General, 1985 (Box 5, Folder 2)
- Thank You Letters for Contributions, 1984 (Box 5, Folder 3)
- Thank You Letters for Contributions, 1984-1985 (Box 5, Folder 4)
- "A" General, 1985 (Box 5, Folder 5)
- AFL-CIO General, 1982-1985 (Box 5, Folder 6)
- Beverly Shulman, 1985 (Box 5, Folder 7)
- AFL-CIO News, 1985 (Box 5, Folder 8)
- AFL-CIO News, 1985 (Box 5, Folder 9)
- Coalition of Labor Union Women (CLUW), 1985 (Box 5, Folder 10)
- Congress, 1985 (Box 5, Folder 11)
- Congressional Record, 1985 (Box 5, Folder 12)
- Congressional Hispanic Caucus, 1985 (Box 5, Folder 13)
- Cope Operating Committee, 1984 (Box 5, Folder 14)
- Cope Report, 1985 (Box 5, Folder 15)
  August 12
- Consumer Legislation, 1985 (Box 5, Folder 16)
- Correspondence Committee, 1985 (Box 5, Folder 17)
- "D" General, 1985 (Box 5, Folder 18)
- Democratic National Committee, 1985 (Box 5, Folder 19)
- Evelyn Dubrow - General Expenses, 1985 (Box 5, Folder 20)
- Iris Sunshine - Expenses, 1983-1985 (Box 5, Folder 21)
- Evelyn Dubrow - Miscellaneous Expenses, 1985-1986 (Box 5, Folder 22)
- Evelyn Dubrow - Miscellaneous, 1984-1985 (Box 5, Folder 23)
- Fashion Show (Congressional), 1985 (Box 5, Folder 24)
- Fiber, Fabric, and Apparel Coalition for Trade, 1985 (Box 5, Folder 25)
- Facts About Congress, 1983-1985 (Box 5, Folder 26)
- G.E.B., 1985 (Box 5, Folder 27)
- General Advisory Council, 1984-1985 (Box 5, Folder 28)
- Material for General Advisory Council, 1985 (Box 5, Folder 29)
  February 1
- Gus Tyler Staff Mailings, 1984-1985 (Box 5, Folder 30)
- "H" General, 1985 (Box 5, Folder 31)
- Housing, 1983-1985 (Box 5, Folder 32)
- Immigration, 1985 (Box 5, Folder 33)
- Imports (807 Tariffs Delegation Schedules), 1985 (Box 5, Folder 34)
- Inter-Office Memos, 1985 (Box 5, Folder 35)
- Miscellaneous, 1984-1985 (Box 5, Folder 36)
- Legislative Newsletter, 1985 (Box 5, Folder 37)
- Lobbying Reports, 1985-1986 (Box 5, Folder 38)
- Miscellaneous, 1985 (Box 5, Folder 39)
- Political Department Invoices, 1985 (Box 6, Folder 1)
- Congress - General, 1985 (Box 6, Folder 2)
- Congress - General, 1985 (Box 6, Folder 3)
- Retirees, 1985-1986 (Box 6, Folder 4)
- Campaign Committee Contributions - Primary and General Elections, 1985 (Box 6, Folder 5)
- Congress, 1985 (Box 6, Folder 6)
- Campaign Committee Miscellaneous Contributions, 1985 (Box 6, Folder 7)
- Campaign Committee Contributions Deficits, 1985 (Box 6, Folder 8)
- Campaign Committee Reports, 1985 (Box 6, Folder 9)
- Campaign Contributions, 1985 (Box 6, Folder 10)
- Material Received from ILGWU Campaign Committee, 1985-1986 (Box 6, Folder 11)
- Material Received from ILGWU Campaign Committee, 1985 (Box 6, Folder 12)
- National Journal - 1986 Campaign Preview, 1985 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  December 7
- Campaign Committee Contributions, 1986 (Box 6, Folder 14)
- Campaign Committee Contributions, 1986 (Box 6, Folder 15)
- Campaign Committee Contributions, 1986 (Box 6, Folder 16)
- Cope Financial Report, 1986 (Box 6, Folder 17)
- Frontlash, 1986 (Box 6, Folder 18)
- Democratic Part of Puerto Rico, 1986 (Box 7, Folder 1)
- Democratic National Committee, 1986 (Box 7, Folder 2)
- Evelyn Dubrow Correspondence, 1986 (Box 7, Folder 3)
- "M" General, 1986 (Box 7, Folder 4)
- Proofs of the GEB Report, 1986 (Box 7, Folder 5)
- Pledge List of Fundraisers, 1986 (Box 7, Folder 6)
- Campaign Committee Collections, 1986 (Box 7, Folder 7)
- Textile and Apparel Override, 1986 (Box 7, Folder 8)
- "W" General, 1986 (Box 7, Folder 9)
- "J" General, 1986 (Box 7, Folder 10)
- "L" General, 1986 (Box 7, Folder 11)
- Lobbying Reports, 1986 (Box 7, Folder 12)
- Legislative Alert, 1985-1986 (Box 7, Folder 13)
- "M" General, 1986 (Box 7, Folder 14)
- Congress - General, 1986 (Box 7, Folder 15)
- Correspondence with Congress, 1986 (Box 7, Folder 16)
- "N" General, 1986 (Box 7, Folder 17)
- Evelyn Dubrow Correspondence, 1986 (Box 7, Folder 18)
- The New Republic, 1986 (Box 7, Folder 19)
- Philadelphia/South Jersey District Council, 1986 (Box 7, Folder 20)
- Beverly Shulman, 1986 (Box 7, Folder 21)
- National Civic Review, 1986 (Box 7, Folder 22)
- The New Republic, 1986 (Box 7, Folder 23)
- Miscellaneous Articles on Homework, 1986 (Box 7, Folder 24)
- The New Republic, 1986 (Box 7, Folder 25)
- The New Republic, 1986 (Box 7, Folder 26)
- Health - General, 1986 (Box 7, Folder 27)
- Housing - General, 1986 (Box 7, Folder 28)
- Thank You Letters, 1986 (Box 8, Folder 1)
- Thank You Letters, 1986 (Box 8, Folder 2)
- Federal Election Commission Report, 1986 (Box 8, Folder 3)
- Federal Election Commission Report, 1986 (Box 8, Folder 4)
- ILGWU Campaign Committee Contributions, 1986 (Box 8, Folder 5)
- Evelyn Dubrow Correspondence, 1985-1986 (Box 8, Folder 6)
- Requests for Contributions, 1986 (Box 8, Folder 7)
- Requests for Contributions, 1986 (Box 8, Folder 8)
- ILGWU Finance Department, 1986 (Box 8, Folder 9)
- ILGWU Finance Department, 1986 (Box 8, Folder 10)
- Campaign Committee District Contributions, 1986 (Box 8, Folder 11)
- Letters of Transmittal, 1986 (Box 8, Folder 12)
- Campaign Committee Miscellaneous Contributions, 1986 (Box 8, Folder 13)
- Express Mail Receipts, 1984-1986 (Box 8, Folder 14)
- Democratic National Party, 1990 (Box 8, Folder 15)
- Democrats for the 90s, 1990 (Box 8, Folder 16)
- Earned Income Credit Campaign, 1990 (Box 8, Folder 17)
- Evelyn Dubrow - Expenses, 1990 (Box 8, Folder 18)
- ILGWU Finance Department, 1990 (Box 8, Folder 19)
- Evelyn Dubrow - Personal Expenses, 1990 (Box 8, Folder 20)
- ILGWU Contributions, 1987-1989 (Box 8, Folder 21)
- AFL-CIO Legislative Alert, 1990 (Box 8, Folder 22)
- AFL-CIO General, 1989-1990 (Box 8, Folder 23)
- Calendar, 1990 (Box 8, Folder 24)
  January-December
- Census Project, 1990 (Box 8, Folder 25)
- Child Care Bill, 1990 (Box 8, Folder 26)
- Coalition of Labor Union Women (CLUW), 1990 (Box 8, Folder 27)
- Senate - General, 1990 (Box 9, Folder 1)
- Thank You for Contributions Letters, 1990 (Box 9, Folder 2)
- Textile, Apparel, and Footwear Trade Act, 1990 (Box 9, Folder 3)
- Payroll Information, 1989-1991 (Box 9, Folder 4)
- Strike Articles, 1990 (Box 9, Folder 5)
- Legislation on Striking, 1990 (Box 9, Folder 6)
- Memos on Strike, 1990 (Box 9, Folder 7)
- ILGWU Finance Department, 1990 (Box 9, Folder 8)
- ILGWU Finance Department, 1990 (Box 9, Folder 9)
- Express Mail Receipts, 1990 (Box 9, Folder 10)
- ILGWU Finance Department, 1990 (Box 9, Folder 11)
- ILGWU Finance Department, 1990 (Box 9, Folder 12)
- New York City Congressional Tour, 1989 (Box 9, Folder 13)
- New York State Festival, 1989 (Box 9, Folder 14)
- Planned Parenthood, 1990 (Box 9, Folder 15)
- Invitations to Dinners and Luncheons, 1990 (Box 9, Folder 16)
- Miscellaneous Newspaper Articles, 1990-1991 (Box 9, Folder 17)
- Miscellaneous Newspaper Articles, 1990 (Box 9, Folder 18)
- Miscellaneous Newspaper Articles, 1990 (Box 9, Folder 19)
- Miscellaneous Newspaper Articles, 1990 (Box 9, Folder 20)
- Trade Bill, 1990 (Box 10, Folder 1)
- Miscellaneous Correspondence and Invitations, 1990 (Box 10, Folder 2)
- Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1990 (Box 10, Folder 3)
- Discuss with Jay Mazur (Rallies, Dinners), 1990 (Box 10, Folder 4)
- National Consumers League, 1987 (Box 10, Folder 5)
- Miscellaneous Newsletters, 1990 (Box 10, Folder 6)
- Justice, 1990 (Box 10, Folder 7)
- AFL-CIO News, 1990 (Box 10, Folder 8)
- Correspondence with Evelyn Dubrow and Jay Mazur, 1990 (Box 10, Folder 9)
- AFL-CIO Healthcare Committee: Background on Major Healthcare Reform Options, 1990 (Box 10, Folder 10)
- Health Care Campaign, 1990 (Box 10, Folder 11)
- Health Care, 1989 (Box 10, Folder 12)
- House Democratic Majority Fund, 1990 (Box 10, Folder 13)
- Housing NOW!, 1990 (Box 10, Folder 14)
- Pauline Newman Pamphlet (Box 10, Folder 15)
- "Homework: A Return to the Industrial Dark Ages of Sweatshops and No Protections" by Jay Mazur, 1986 (Box 10, Folder 16)
- The New Leader, 1988 (Box 10, Folder 17)
  October 31
- Import Coordinators and Trade Bill, 1990 (Box 10, Folder 18)
- Correspondence with Jay Mazur, 1990 (Box 10, Folder 19)
- AFL-CIO IUD, 1990 (Box 10, Folder 20)
- Number of Signatures According to Each Local, District, Etc., 1990 (Box 10, Folder 21)
- Responses from Trade Coordinators, 1990 (Box 10, Folder 22)
- Textile, Apparel, and Footwear Trade Act, 1990 (Box 10, Folder 23)
- Correspondence Regarding Trade, 1990 (Box 10, Folder 24)
- FFACT Information, 1990 (Box 10, Folder 25)
- Express Mail Receipts, 1990 (Box 10, Folder 26)
- Retiree Information, 1990 (Box 10, Folder 27)
- Union Label, 1990 (Box 10, Folder 28)
- Updates, 1990 (Box 10, Folder 29)
- Congress - General, 1990 (Box 10, Folder 30)
- Congress - General, 1990 (Box 10, Folder 31)
- Requests for Contributions and Receptions, 1992-1994 (Box 11, Folder 1)
- Requests for Contributions and Receptions, 1992-1994 (Box 11, Folder 2)
- Requests for Contributions and Receptions, 1993 (Box 11, Folder 3)
- Requests for Contributions and Receptions, 1993 (Box 11, Folder 4)
- ILGWU Campaign Committee, 1993 (Box 11, Folder 5)
- Invitations to Congressmen Receptions, 1992-1993 (Box 11, Folder 6)
- ILGWU State and Local Election Fund and Campaign Committee, 1993 (Box 11, Folder 7)
- Thank You Letters, 1993 (Box 11, Folder 8)
- Federal Elections Commission, 1993 (Box 11, Folder 9)
- ILGWU Campaign Committee, 1993 (Box 11, Folder 10)
- Contributions to ILGWU Campaign Committee, 1985-1992 (Box 11, Folder 11)
- Thank You Letters, 1992 (Box 11, Folder 12)
- Contributions and Receptions, 1992-1993 (Box 11, Folder 13)
- Contributions and Receptions, 1992 (Box 11, Folder 14)
- Contributions and Receptions, 1992 (Box 11, Folder 15)
- Contributions and Receptions, 1992-1993 (Box 11, Folder 16)
- ILGWU Campaign Committee and State and Local Election Fund, 1992 (Box 12, Folder 1)
- ILGWU Campaign Committee and State and Local Election Fund, 1992 (Box 12, Folder 2)
- Federal Elections Commission, 1992 (Box 12, Folder 3)
- ILGWU Campaign Committee and State and Local Election Fund, 1991-1992 (Box 12, Folder 4)
- ILGWU Campaign Committee, 1992 (Box 12, Folder 5)
- ILGWU Campaign Committee Contributions to Primary Candidates, 1992 (Box 12, Folder 6)
- ILGWU Campaign Committee - Miscellaneous Contributions, 1992 (Box 12, Folder 7)
- ILGWU Campaign Committee, 1992 (Box 12, Folder 8)
- Photographs (Box 12, Folder 9)
- David Wells Correspondence, 1992 (Box 12, Folder 10)
- ILGWU Political Department - Miscellaneous, 1992 (Box 12, Folder 11)
- Evelyn Dubrow - Correspondence, 1992 (Box 12, Folder 12)
- Thank You Letters to Evelyn Dubrow, 1992 (Box 12, Folder 13)
- 32nd Senate District Democratic Telephones, 1992 (Box 12, Folder 14)
- Congress - General, 1991-1992 (Box 12, Folder 15)
- Miscellaneous Articles, 1992 (Box 12, Folder 16)
- Miscellaneous Articles, 1992 (Box 12, Folder 17)
- Miscellaneous Articles, 1992 (Box 12, Folder 18)
- Miscellaneous Articles, 1992 (Box 13, Folder 1)
- Miscellaneous Articles, 1992 (Box 13, Folder 2)
- OHSA Reform, 1991-1992 (Box 13, Folder 3)
- Express Mail Receipts, 1992-1993 (Box 13, Folder 4)
- Dr. Starobin, 1992 (Box 13, Folder 5)
- Health Care, 1992 (Box 13, Folder 6)
- Health Care, 1992 (Box 13, Folder 7)
- Housing, 1992 (Box 13, Folder 8)
- International Association of Political Consultants, 1991-1992 (Box 13, Folder 9)
- Industrial Union Department (AFL-CIO IUD), 1992 (Box 13, Folder 10)
- ILGWU Convention Committee, 1992 (Box 13, Folder 11)
- AFL-CIO News, 1992 (Box 13, Folder 12)
- Justice, 1992 (Box 13, Folder 13)
- Labor-Industry Coalition for International Trade (LICIT), 1992 (Box 13, Folder 14)
- Labor-Management Cooperation Grant Program, 1989 (Box 13, Folder 15)
- Jay Mazur Correspondence, 1992 (Box 13, Folder 16)
- "C" General, 1992 (Box 13, Folder 17)
- AFL-CIO General, 1992 (Box 13, Folder 18)
- AFL-CIO General, 1992 (Box 13, Folder 19)
- AFL-CIO General, 1992 (Box 13, Folder 20)
- "N" General, 1991-1992 (Box 13, Folder 21)
- National Women's Political Caucus, 1992 (Box 13, Folder 22)
- Freedom of Choice Act, 1992 (Box 13, Folder 23)
- Miscellaneous Articles (Trade, Health Care, Etc.), 1992 (Box 13, Folder 24)
- Miscellaneous Articles (Trade, Health Care, Etc.), 1992 (Box 13, Folder 25)
- Miscellaneous Articles (Trade, Health Care), 1992 (Box 13, Folder 26)
- Miscellaneous Articles (Trade, Child Care), 1992 (Box 14, Folder 1)
- Articles on Congress, 1992 (Box 14, Folder 2)
- Articles on Congress, 1992 (Box 14, Folder 3)
- Haiti, 1992 (Box 14, Folder 4)
- Citizen Trade Watch, 1992 (Box 14, Folder 5)
- "A" General, 1992 (Box 14, Folder 6)
- ILGWU Convention Committee, 1992 (Box 14, Folder 7)
- Silver Needle Award - Retiree Service Department, 1992 (Box 14, Folder 8)
- Report of Proceedings of the 40th Convention of the ILGWU, 1989 (Box 14, Folder 9)
  June
- Election Disbursements, US Senate Campaign Committee, 1991-1992 (Box 14, Folder 10)
- "A" General, 1992 (Box 14, Folder 11)
- Evelyn Dubrow - Miscellaneous, 1992 (Box 14, Folder 12)
- Evelyn Dubrow - Medical Insurance, 1992 (Box 14, Folder 13)
- Evelyn Dubrow - Expenses, 1992 (Box 14, Folder 14)
- New York - General, 1992 (Box 14, Folder 15)
- Education - General, 1991-1992 (Box 14, Folder 16)
- Democratic Senatorial Campaign Committee, 1992 (Box 14, Folder 17)
- Democratic National Convention, 1992 (Box 14, Folder 18)
- Democratic National Convention, 1992 (Box 14, Folder 19)
- Democratic National Committee, 1992 (Box 14, Folder 20)